thepostmansknock.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy – The Postman's Knock

## Personal Identification Information

Personal identification information {e.g. name, email address, address} is collected in a number of ways. This includes when you visit thepostmansknock.com, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form; or participate in other activities, services, features or resources I make available on The Postman’s Knock. You may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address. You may, however, visit the site anonymously. Personal identification information will be accepted from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to this site. You can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent you from engaging in site-related activities {i.e. ordering a product}.

YOUR PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION WILL NEVER BE SHARED WITH A THIRD PARTY. I may retain your information in order to send updates {i.e. with digital files}; send a thank you card, etc. If, however, you wish for your personal information to be erased from my records, you need only ask.

## Non-Personal Identification Information

The Postman’s Knock may collect non-personal identification information about you whenever you interact with the website. Non-personal identification information may include your browser name {Firefox, Safari, etc.}, the type of computer and technical information about your means of connection to the website, such as the operating system, and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

_Why is this information collected?_ The Postman’s Knock collects this information for a number of reasons. If I know which browsers my users are utilizing to view the site, it’s easier for me to optimize your experience {e.g. make the site Internet Explorer-friendly; avoid using the Flash plug-in}. The goal is to constantly improve this site to give you the best experience possible.

## Web Browser Cookies

The Postman’s Knock may use “cookies” to enhance your experience on the site. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about you — like recognizing you when you revisit the site. You absolutely may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent.

## How The Postman’s Knock Uses Collected Information

The Postman’s Knock may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To improve customer service:_  
Information you provide helps me to respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _To improve thepostmansknock.com:_  
I may use feedback you provide to improve the products and services offered on this website.
  * _To process payments:_  
I may use the information that you provide about yourself when placing an order only to provide service to that order. I do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * _To run a promotion, contest, survey or other website feature:_  
I will only send you information you have agreed to receive about topics I think will be of interest to you.
  * _To send periodic emails:_  
I may use your email address to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. It may also be used to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If you decide to opt-in to The Postman’s Knock mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, I include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email, or you may contact me via this website.

## How Your Information is Protected **  
**

I adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on thepostmansknock.com.

## Sharing Your Personal Information

I DO NOT — AND WILL  NOT — SELL, TRADE, OR RENT YOUR PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION TO OTHERS. I may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with my business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers {for example, I may let partners/advertisers know how many site views the TPK site gets on average, and your views will count in that average}. I also may use third-party service providers to help me operate The Postman’s Knock/thepostmansknock.com or administer activities on my behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys {MailChimp}. I may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given me your permission.

## Third Party Websites

You may find advertising or other content on The Postman’s Knock that links to the sites and services of my partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. I do not control the content or links that appear on these sites, and I am not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from thepostmansknock.com. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to my Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

## Advertising

Ads appearing on thepostmansknock.com may be delivered to you by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to thepostmansknock.com and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non-personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

The Postman’s Knock has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When I do, I will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. I encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how I am helping to protect the personal information I collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using thepostmansknock.com, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not patronize this website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting Me **  
**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact me at:

Lindsey Bugbee  
The Postman’s Knock  
+1 (785) 443-0354

This article was last modified on February 18, 2019
